A Guide to the University of Virginia Health System Marketing Communications collection, 1857-2006, bulk 1950-2000
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Series I: Departmental materials, 1907-2002
  - Medicine, circa 1956-2004
    - Edward W. Hook, Internal Medicine, with unidentified others 1988 June (Box-folder 2:62)
    - Thier Lecture at the Medical School Auditorium, Internal Medicine, 1989 January 24 (Box-folder 2:63)
    - Edward Hook, Internal Medicine, 1990 March 20 (Box-folder 2:64)
      Photograph by J. Biondo
    - John Marshall, Internal Medicine, 1991 (Box-folder 2:65)
    - Charles Crockett (Assistant Dean of Medicine) with Bryd Leavell and Donald Shotton (?), Internal Medicine, undated (Box-folder 2:66)
    - Thomas H. Hunter as an infant, undated (Box-folder 2:67)
    - Thomas H. Hunter (Internal Medicine) and a photograph of a Turlington’s Balsam glass bottle and an unidentified x-ray, undated (Box-folder 2:68)
      Glass bottle photograph and x-ray were in an envelope marked Dr. Hunter
    - Thomas H. Hunter’s house, undated (Box-folder 2:69)
    - William Parsons, Department of Medicine, Chair, undated (Box-folder 2:70)
    - William Parsons, Department of Medicine, Chair, undated (Box-folder 2:71)
    - J. Edwin Wood, Tate?, and John Guerrant, Internal Medicine, undated (Box-folder 2:72)
      John Guerrant seated with triangle measuring device in second image
    - Internal Medicine Group, with Edward Hook, 1987 (Box-folder 2:73)
    - Internal Medicine Group, with Edward Hook, 1988 June 24, 2:74
    - Internal Medicine Groups, with George Beller, ?Lindsay, Cathy Murphy?, and ?Feitch 1988 (Box-folder 2:75)
    - Internal Medicine Group, with Edward Hook, 1989 (Box-folder 2:76)
    - Internal Medicine Groups, with Edward Hook, 1990 May 24 (Box-folder 2:77)
    - Internal Medicine Group, with John Marshall, 1991 June (Box-folder 2:78)
    - Department of Medicine First Year House Officers, circa 1991 (Box-folder 2:79)
    - Internal Medicine Group, 1992 (Box-folder 2:80)
    - Internal Medicine First Year Residents, 2002 (Box-folder 2:81)
    - Internal Medicine Group, with Edward Hook, undated (Box-folder 2:82)
  - Neurology, 1986-2002
    - Neurology Group, 1986 (Box-folder 2:83)
    - Neurology Group, with T.R. Johns, George Hanna, Soo Ik Lee, and Fritz (Fred) Dreifuss, 1987 (Box-folder 2:84)
    - Neurology Group, 1988 (Box-folder 2:85)
    - Neurology Group, 1989 May 12 (Box-folder 2:86)
    - G. Frederick Wooten, Neurology, Chair 1990 May 25 (Box-folder 2:87)
      Photographed by J. Biondo in McKim Hall
    - Neurology Group, with Fred Wooten, Chair, 1990 June 22 (Box-folder 2:88)
    - Blue Ridge Hospital Neurology, Epilepsy Unit, with Fritz Dreifuss, 1991 March 1 (Box-folder 2:89)
    - Neurology Group, with Fred Wooten, Chair, 1991 June (Box-folder 2:90)
    - Fritz Dreifuss, Neurology, 1991 (Box-folder 2:91)
    - Neurology Group, 1992 (Box-folder 2:92)
    - James Q. Miller, Neurology, 2002 January (Box-folder 2:93)
    - T. R. Johns, Neurology, Chair, undated (Box-folder 2:94)
    - Karen C. Johnston, Neurology, undated (Box-folder 2:95)
    - Mark S. Quigg, Neurology, undated (Box-folder 2:96)
    - George Frederick Wooten, Neurology, undated (Box-folder 2:97)
    - George Frederick Wooten, Neurology, undated (Box-folder 2:98)
  - Neurosurgery, 1988-2003
    - Neurosurgery Group, with John A. Jane, 1988 April (Box-folder 2:99)
    - Neurosurgery Group, with John Jane, John Ashley, and Robert Carey, 1988 (Box-folder 2:100)
      John Ashley center front with tie, Robert Carey front with slides, John Jane on J. Ashley’s right.
    - John A. Jane, Neurosurgery, 1989 November 21 (Box-folder 2:101)
      Photo taken by C. Hodge in Private Clinics, 1st Floor
    - Neal Kassell, Neurosurgery, 1989 November 30 (Box-folder 2:102)
    - Neal Kassell, Neurosurgery, 1990 April 2 (Box-folder 2:103)
      Photo taken by J. Biondo in Private Clinics, 1st Floor
    - Neurosurgery Group, with John Jane, 1990 (Box-folder 2:104)
    - Neurosurgery Group, with John Jane, 1991 (Box-folder 2:105)
    - Neurosurgery Group, 1992 (Box-folder 2:106)
    - Neal F. Kassell, Neurosurgery, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 2:107)
      Image from 2002-2003 issue of Health Talk
    - W. Gayle Crutchfield and Juan de Dios Martinez Galindo, Neurosurgery, undated (Box-folder 2:108)
    - Gayle Crutchfield operating on a patient, Neurosurgery, undated (Box-folder 2:109)
    - Gayle Crutchfield portraits and performing surgery, Neurosurgery, undated (Box-folder 2:110)
    - The Gamma Knife, Leskell Gamma Unit, undated (Box-folder 2:111)
    - Imaging of a skull, Cosgrove, Neurosurgery undated (Box-folder 2:112)
    - ? Lee, Neurosurgery, undated (Box-folder 2:113)
    - Juan de Dios Martinez Galindo, Neurosurgery, undated (Box-folder 2:114)
    - Jason P. Sheehan, Neurosurgery, undated (Box-folder 2:115)
    - Ladislau Steiner, Gamma Knife, and John B. Selby, Tube Dressing, undated (Box-folder 2:116)
  - Nursing, circa 1918-1992
    - Josephine McLeod, in Atlanta?, circa 1918 June 21 (Box-folder 2:117)
    - Josephine McLeod, circa 1920s-30s (Box-folder 2:118)
    - Nurses in the Old Hospital, Barringer (?) Ward, circa 1930 (Box-folder 2:119)
    - B. Ward Nurses with children, 1945 December 21 (Box-folder 2:120)
    - School of Nursing Catalog Photographs, 1947 (Box-folder 2:121)
    - Nursing Education, 1969 Fall (Box-folder 2:122)
    - Nursing Services, 1970 May (Box-folder 2:123)
    - B. Jeanette Lancaster, Dean of the School of Nursing, 1989 November 21 (Box-folder 2:124)
    - Kellog Nursing Grant, with Linda Davies, 1990 October 30 (Box-folder 2:125)
    - Nursing School Pinning Ceremony, 1992 May 16 (Box-folder 2:126)
    - Pamela Cipriano, School of Nursing, undated (Box-folder 2:127)
    - Pamela D. Dennison, School of Nursing, undated (Box-folder 2:128)
    - Pat Dougherty, Certified Nurse Midwife at the Midlife Health Center, undated (Box-folder 2:129)
    - Kathleen (Kathy) Fletcher, School of Nursing, undated (Box-folder 2:130)
    - Historic Nursing photographs, undated (Box-folder 2:131)
    - M. Kite and M. Kline, Nursing?, undated (Box-folder 2:132)
    - Labor and Delivery Nursing, (Anderson?), undated (Box-folder 2:133)
    - Nurse with a patient, (Mortensen?), undated (Box-folder 2:134)
    - Nursing Group photographs (including a graduation scene), and nurses with patients, undated (Box-folder 2:135)
    - Nursing Groups, with Vivian Dodson, undated (Box-folder 2:136)
    - Subsidiary Nursing, undated (Box-folder 2:137)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1965-2002
    - William A. Scoggin, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1965 October 26 (Box-folder 2:138)
    - James D. Kitchin III, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1968 May 2 (Box-folder 2:139)
    - Bruce G. Bateman, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1988 June 6 (Box-folder 2:140)
    - Buswai, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1988 June (Box-folder 2:141)
    - James E. Ferguson, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1988 June (Box-folder 2:142)
    - Guy M. Harbert, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1988 June (Box-folder 2:143)
    - Hoge (Hogge?), Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1988 June (Box-folder 2:144)
    - James D. Kitchin, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1988 June (Box-folder 2:145)
    - Kutzner, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1988 June (Box-folder 2:146)
    - Peyton T. Taylor, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1988 June (Box-folder 2:147)
    - Siva Thiagarajah, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1988 June (Box-folder 2:148)
    - Paul Underwood, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1988 June (Box-folder 2:149)
    - Paul Underwood, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1989 November 30 (Box-folder 2:150)
    - Peyton T. Taylor, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1989 December 6 (Box-folder 2:151)
    - James Kitchin, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1989 December 14 (Box-folder 2:152)
    - Guy M. Harbert, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1990 January 18 (Box-folder 2:153)
    - Paul Underwood, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1991 May (Box-folder 2:154)
    - Frederick Frank, Obstetrics and Gynecology, Intern, Resident, and Chief Resident (1998-2002), circa 2000 (Box-folder 2:155)
    - Don Armstrong, Obstetrics and Gynecology Resident, circa 2001, 2:156
    - Melanie Leight, Obstetrics and Gynecology, Resident, circa 2002 (Box-folder 2:157)
    - Hospital Examination Room, undated (Box-folder 2:158)
    - Labor and Delivery instrument tray, undated (Box-folder 2:159)
    - John Nokes, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box-folder 2:160)
    - Colleen Raymond, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box-folder 2:161)
    - William Norman Thornton, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box-folder 2:162)
    - William Norman Thornton, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box-folder 2:163)
    - Uterine Brushes, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box-folder 2:164)
    - Joseph Whelan and Jennifer Wenger, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box-folder 2:165)
    - Lester Wilson, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box-folder 2:166)
  - Orthopedics and Rehabilitation, 1939-1990
    - Charles J. Frankel diplomas and certificates (copies), Orthopedic Surgery, 1939-1959 (Box-folder 2:167)
    - ”Dr. Frankel Praises Coach McDonald,” Medical Alumni News Letter, 1953 December (Box-folder 2:168)
      Article on Charles Frankel, Orthopedic Surgery & Sports Medicine
    - Physical Therapy, 1970 May (Box-folder 2:169)
    - Occupational Therapy, circa 1970 (Box-folder 2:170)
    - Frank McCue, Orthopedics, 1987 September (Box-folder 2:171)
    - Orthopedics Group on the steps of the Rotunda, with Warren G. Stamp, Chair 1988 June (Box-folder 2:172)
    - Warren G. Stamp, Orthopedics, 1989 November 21 (Box-folder 2:173)
    - Gary Balian, Orthopedics / Biochemistry and Molecular Genetics, 1989 November 22 (Box-folder 2:174)
      Photographed by C. Hodge at Cobb Hall
    - Orthopedics Clinic Group, with Warren G. Stamp, 1990 June 9 (Box-folder 2:175)
    - Orthopedics Group, with McHugh?, 1990 July (Box-folder 2:176)
    - J. Hamilton Allen, Orthopedics, undated (Box-folder 2:177)
    - Richard T. Ergenbright, Orthopedics, undated (Box-folder 2:178)
    - Charles J. Frankel (in bow tie), ? Wilkinson, and ? Myers, Orthopedics, undated (Box-folder 2:179)
    - Frank C. McCue, Orthopedics and Rehabilitation, undated (Box-folder 2:180)
    - Gloves/Sports Equipment, Orthopedics, undated (Box-folder 2:181)
    - Orthopedics Group at the Boar’s Head Inn, with Lou Ruland, undated (Box-folder 2:182)
    - Orthopedics Surgery Group, with Warren G. Stamp, undated (Box-folder 2:183)
      Photographs taken outside Private Clinics entrance and in 1929 Medical Education Building foyer
    - Rehabilitation Techniques and Equipment, undated (Box-folder 2:184)
  - Otolaryngology, 1953-1991
    - Cary N. Moon, Otolaryngology, 1953 June (Box-folder 3:1)
    - Cary N. Moon, Otolaryngology, 1961 June, 3:2
    - Robert Jahrsdoerfer, Otolaryngology, 1967 February (Box-folder 3:3)
    - Otolaryngology Group, with Robert Cantrell, 1986 (Box-folder 3:4)
    - Otolaryngology Group, with Robert Cantrell, 1989 June 15 (Box-folder 3:5)
    - Robert Cantrell, Otolaryngology - Head and Neck Surgery, 1989 November 21 (Box-folder 3:6)
    - Otolaryngology Group, with G. Slaughter Fitz-Hugh and Robert Cantrell, 1990 June 21 (Box-folder 3:7)
    - Otolaryngology Group at the Boar’s Head Inn, with Robert Cantrell, 1991 June 20 (Box-folder 3:8)
    - George Hashisaki, Otolaryngology - Head and Neck Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Halstead S. Hedges, Otolaryngology, undated (Box-folder 3:10)
    - W. Copley McLean, Otolaryngology, undated (Box-folder 3:11)
    - Cary N. Moon, Otolaryngology, undated (Box-folder 3:12)
    - Fletcher D. Woodward, Otolaryngology, undated (Box-folder 3:13)
  - Pathology, circa 1951-2001
    - M. Shannon Allen, Pathology, circa 1951-1961 (Box-folder 3:14)
    - Catherine Russell, Pathology/Microbiology, circa 1955 (Box-folder 3:15)
    - James R. Cash, Pathology, 1958 May and undated (Box-folder 3:16)
    - Martin Netsky, Pathology, circa 1962-1963 (Box-folder 3:17)
    - David E. Smith, Pathology, Chair, circa 1960s (Box-folder 3:18)
    - David E. Smith performing his 10,000th autopsy, 1964 October (Box-folder 3:19)
    - Pathology Department flood damage, 1987 September (Box-folder 3:20)
    - Christopher Paul Crum, Gynecologic Pathology, 1988 June (Box-folder 3:21)
    - Pathology Group, with Thomas W. Tillack, Chair, 1989 (Box-folder 3:22)
    - Pathology Group, with Thomas W. Tillack, Chair, 1990 (Box-folder 3:23)
    - Pathology Group, with Thomas W. Tillack, Chair, 1991 (Box-folder 3:24)
    - Pathology Group, with Thomas W. Tillack, 1992 (Box-folder 3:25)
    - Joanna Steer, Pathology Resident, circa 2001 (Box-folder 3:26)
    - Oliver B. Bobbitt, Pathology, and Hematocrit Graphic Reader undated (Box-folder 3:27)
      Graphic reader in envelope labeled O.B. Bobbitt
    - William E. Bray, Clinical Pathology, undated (Box-folder 3:28)
    - Helen P. Cathro, Pathology, undated (Box-folder 3:29)
    - Yin-Tang Hsu, Pathology, undated (Box-folder 3:30)
    - Harry Marshall, Pathology, undated (Box-folder 3:31)
    - James R. Mize, Pathology, undated (Box-folder 3:32)
    - Lucien Rubenstein and group with microscopes, undated (Box-folder 3:33)
  - Pediatrics, circa 1940s-2002
    - Rucker Home for Children, circa 1940s (Box-folder 3:34)
    - Martha Carpenter, Pediatrics, 1965 November (Box-folder 3:35)
    - Pediatrics Group, with William G. Thurman, Chair, 1969 May 27 (Box-folder 3:36)
    - Pediatrics, 2nd floor, 1987 March 20 (Box-folder 3:37)
      Kelsey, Flanik, Saulsbury
    - Pediatrics Group, 1987 June 19 (Box-folder 3:38)
    - Children’s Rehabilitation Center Education Services, 1987 (Box-folder 3:39)
    - California Raisin visits pediatrics patients on W-2, 1988 November 1 (Box-folder 3:40)
    - Pediatrics Group, 1988 (Box-folder 3:41)
    - Richard Kesler, Pediatrics, 1989 November (Box-folder 3:42)
    - Robert Blizzard, Pediatrics, 1989 December (Box-folder 3:43)
    - Robert J. “Butch” Roberts, Pediatrics, 1989 December (Box-folder 3:44)
    - Pediatrics photographs for textbook, with Mary W. Clark, Jacob A. Lohr, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 3:45)
    - Nerancy Neonatal Intensive Care Unit, 1990 January 26 (Box-folder 3:46)
    - Summer Kids Group outside the Physics Building, President’s Office1990 June 29 (Box-folder 3:47)
    - UVA Child Care Center Groundbreaking, 1990 October 12 (Box-folder 3:48)
    - Robert J. “Butch” Roberts, Pediatrics, Chair, circa 1990 (Box-folder 3:49)
    - Virginia Power Newborn Nursery, with Don Detmer, 1991 September (Box-folder 3:50)
    - Sharon Hostler, Pediatrics/Kluge Children’s Rehabilitation Center, 1991 (Box-folder 3:51)
    - Kluge Children’s Rehabilitation Center Christmas Party, 1992 December (Box-folder 3:52)
    - Thomas D. Lamkin, Pediatrics, 2001 (Box-folder 3:53)
    - Pediatrics staff photos, 2002 June 21 (Box-folder 3:54)
      Pictured: Grant Mussma, Devon Elizabeth Ebbing, Jessica Simmons, Laurissa Richter, Karyn Frye, Carol Boersma, Peter DeVries, Laura Lee Swan, Jonathan Swanson, Cary Sauer, Anita Swamy
    - John Barcia, Pediatric Nephrology, undated (Box-folder 3:55)
    - Robert Blizzard and McLemore Birdsong Party, Pediatrics, undated (Box-folder 3:56)
    - Patrick Brown and Ronald Turner, Pediatrics, undated (Box-folder 3:57)
    - Martha Carpenter, Pediatrics, undated (Box-folder 3:58)
    - Children’s Medical Center Mascot Bear, undated (Box-folder 3:59)
      Images for The Link
    - Children’s Rehabilitation Center marketing photographs with Janet Allaire?, undated (Box-folder 3:60)
    - Inhalation Therapy, with W. Gerald Teague (Pediatrics), undated (Box-folder 3:61)
    - Ellen Lawton at the Children’s Rehabilitation Center with a new speaking device, undated (Box-folder 3:62)
    - Neonatal Intensive Care Unit, with John Kattwinkel, undated (Box-folder 3:63)
    - Neonatal Intensive Care Unit, with R. Morrison, undated (Box-folder 3:64)
    - Neonatal Intensive Care Unit marketing photograph, undated (Box-folder 3:65)
    - Newborn Emergency Transport, undated (Box-folder 3:66)
    - Newborn Emergency Transport System at UVA Children’s Hospital, undated (Box-folder 3:67)
    - Marcus Shaker, Pediatrics Resident, undated (Box-folder 3:68)
    - Portrait of William Wirt Waddell, Jr., Pediatrics, undated (Box-folder 3:69)
  - Pharmacy, 1965-1990
    - Pharmacy and Central Sterile Supply, 1965 (Box-folder 3:70)
    - Hospital Pharmacy, 1990 November 15 (Box-folder 3:71)
      Davis?
    - Locke Boyer and Sharon Boyer in the Pharmacy, undated (Box-folder 3:72)
    - Hospital Pharmacy and technicians, undated (Box-folder 3:73)
  - Plastic and Maxillofacial Surgery, circa 1971-1991
    - Milton T. Edgerton, Plastic and Maxillofacial Surgery, Chair, circa 1971 (Box-folder 3:74)
    - Raymond G. Morgan, Plastic and Maxillofacial Surgery, Chair, 1990 July 10 (Box-folder 3:75)
    - Plastic Surgery Conference Group, with Raymond Morgan, 1991 May (Box-folder 3:76)
    - Plastic Surgery Conference Group, 1991 (Box-folder 3:77)
  - Radiation Oncology, 1989-1992
    - Radiation Oncology Group, with Jenkins?, 1989 June 2 (Box-folder 3:78)
    - Radiation Therapy, with Nancy Taylor, 1991 February 13 (Box-folder 3:79)
    - Moser Radiation Center, 1992 April 4 (Box-folder 3:80)
    - Radiation Therapy Machine, undated (Box-folder 3:81)
  - Radiology, 1959-1991
    - George Cooper, Jr., Radiology, 1959 January 13 (Box-folder 3:82)
    - 1985 Graduates of the Radiology Technology Program, 1985 (Box-folder 3:83)
    - 1987 Graduates of the Radiology Technology Program, 1987 (Box-folder 3:84)
    - MRI Unit, with Charles Teates, 1987 (Box-folder 3:85)
    - Radiology Group, with Theodore Keats, Chair, 1987 (Box-folder 3:86)
    - CT Scan/MRI, with Terry Tressler, 1989 October 16 (Box-folder 3:87)
    - Radiology Special Procedures, with Dennis Bair, 1989 December 15 - 1990 January 3 (Box-folder 3:88)
    - Transcranial Dopler, Neurovascular Lab, Angio Suite, NNICU, 2nd floor of the new university hospital1990 January 12 (Box-folder 3:89)
      Dr. Wang posed as a patient, with Karen Parks and Lori Elder?
    - Images for Radiology brochure, 1990 November 19 (Box-folder 3:90)
    - Mammography, with Ellen DeParedes, 1991 March 21 (Box-folder 3:91)
    - Ellen DeParedes, Radiology, 1991 August 22 (Box-folder 3:92)
    - Edward E. DeLange, Radiology, 1991 (Box-folder 3:93)
    - George Cooper, Jr., Radiology, undated (Box-folder 3:94)
    - Theodore E. Keats, Radiology, Chair, undated (Box-folder 3:95)
    - Radiology Office, undated (Box-folder 3:96)
    - Radiology Staff, William Brant, Juan M. Olazagasti, Jonathan Ciambotti undated (Box-folder 3:97)
    - Tegtmeyer Special Procedures Room, named for radiologist Charles Tegtmeyer, undated (Box-folder 3:98)
  - Student Health, 1987-2001
    - Student Health staff, with Richard Keeling, Director, 1987 February (Box-folder 3:99)
    - Christine Peterson, Gynecology/Elson Student Health Center, 2001 (Box-folder 3:100)
  - Surgery, 1954-2002
    - Surgery Group, with C. Bruce Morton II, 1954 (Box-folder 3:101)
    - George R. Minor, Surgery, 1955 July (Box-folder 3:102)
    - E. Meredith Aldrich, Pediatric Surgery, 1956 September (Box-folder 3:103)
    - William R. Sandusky, Surgery, 1958 January (Box-folder 3:104)
    - J. Francis “Frank” Dammann, Jr., Surgery, 1958 December 15 (Box-folder 3:105)
    - William H. Muller, Surgery, V.P. for Health Affairs 1963 September 17 (Box-folder 3:106)
    - Surgery Housestaff, with William H. Muller, 1964 June 6 (Box-folder 3:107)
    - William H. Muller, Surgery, V.P. for Health Affairs 1964 June 23 (Box-folder 3:108)
    - Stanton Nolan, Surgery, 1965 January 6 (Box-folder 3:109)
    - George R. Minor, Surgery, 1965 May 14 (Box-folder 3:110)
    - George R. Minor, Surgery, 1967 April (Box-folder 3:111)
    - Leslie Rudolph, Surgery, 1970 August 16 (Box-folder 3:112)
    - Surgery Group, with William H. Muller, Charles Bruce Morton, and Cato Drash, circa 1970 (Box-folder 3:113)
    - Anthony Shaw, Pediatric Surgery, 1971 February 2 (Box-folder 3:114)
    - William H. Muller, Surgery, 1979 October, 3:115
    - Operating Room Instructional photographs, 1986 December 6 (Box-folder 3:116)
    - Don E. Detmer, Surgery, 1987 (Box-folder 3:117)
    - Surgery Group, with Rayford Scott Jones (Chair), 1987 (Box-folder 3:118)
    - Don E. Detmer, Surgery, from Helix, circa 1987-88 (Box-folder 3:119)
    - Don E. Detmer, Surgery, in his office and on the Lawn, 1988 February 10 (Box-folder 3:120)
    - Surgery Group, 1988 (Box-folder 3:121)
    - Don E. Detmer, Surgery, 1988 March 24-1990 (Box-folder 3:122)
    - Surgery classroom and lab, with ?Clark, 1989 January 9 (Box-folder 3:123)
      From Diabetes Center brochure
    - Surgery Group, 1989 April 19 (Box-folder 3:124)
    - Unidentified member of the Surgery Department, 1989 Spring (Box-folder 3:125)
    - General Surgery Group, with Bruce D. Schirmer, 1989 June 14 (Box-folder 3:126)
    - Transplant Clinic, 1989 November 10 (Box-folder 3:127)
    - Rayford Scott Jones, Surgery, 1990 February 12 (Box-folder 3:128)
    - Don E. Detmer, Surgery, 1990 March 6 (Box-folder 3:129)
    - Don E. Detmer with a patient, 1990 March (Box-folder 3:130)
    - Rayford Scott Jones, Surgery Chair, with David Cooke of the Charlottesville-Albemarle Rescue Squad, 1990 June 28 (Box-folder 3:131)
    - Irving L. Kron, Surgery, 1990 July 24 (Box-folder 3:132)
    - Surgery Group, 1990 (Box-folder 3:133)
    - Group photograph with John B. Hanks, Division Head of General Surgery, 1991 May 3, 3:134
    - John B. Hanks, General Surgery, 1991 June (Box-folder 3:135)
    - Surgery Awards, with R. Scott Jones, Surgery Chair, 1991 June 8 (Box-folder 3:136)
    - Irving L. Kron, Surgery, 1991 July (Box-folder 3:137)
    - Steven M. Fiser, Surgery Resident, circa 2000 (Box-folder 3:138)
    - Jeff Claridge, Surgery Resident, circa 2002 (Box-folder 3:139)
    - Ivan Crosby, Thoracic and Cardiovascular Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:140)
    - Ivan K. Crosby, Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:141)
    - J. Francis Dammann, Jr., Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:142)
    - Don E. Detmer, Medical Education/Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:143)
    - E. Cato Drash, Thoracic Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:144)
    - David R. Jones, Thoracic Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:145)
    - Rayford Scott Jones, Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:146)
    - Edwin P. Lehman, Surgery, and unidentified specimen from Mrs. Lena Gordon, envelope marked Dr. Lehmanundated (Box-folder 3:147)
    - Dr. and Mrs. (?) Edwin Lehman, Surgery, and unidentifiedundated (Box-folder 3:148)
    - George R. Minor, Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:149)
    - George R. Minor, Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:150)
    - C. Bruce Morton II, Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:151)
    - William H. Muller, Surgery, V.P. for Health Affairsundated (Box-folder 3:152)
    - Leslie Rudolph, Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:153)
    - Craig L. Slingluff, Surgery, undated (Box-folder 3:154)
    - Miscellaneous Surgery photographs, for William Muller, undated (Box-folder 3:155)
  - Urology, 1941-2002
    - Urology Department: offices, waiting rooms, exam rooms, 1941 September 11 (Box-folder 3:156)
    - Arthur Wyker, Urology, 1962 February 6 (Box-folder 3:157)
    - Urology Group, 1987 May 1 (Box-folder 3:158)
    - Urology Group, with Jay Gillenwater, 1989 April 27 (Box-folder 3:159)
    - Vest Conference Group, with Jay Gillenwater, Urology Chair, 1990 March 6 (Box-folder 3:160)
    - Lithotriptor, with Jay Gillenwater, 1991 January 3 (Box-folder 3:161)
    - Urology Group, with Jay Gillenwater, Chair, 1991 June (Box-folder 3:162)
    - Urology Group, with Jay Gillenwater, Chair, 1992 June (Box-folder 3:163)
    - Urology Group, with Jay Gillenwater, 2002 (Box-folder 3:164)
    - Lithostar machine, with Alan D. Jenkins and Jay Gillenwater, undated (Box-folder 3:165)